Capital District Reference; Collection mss157
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Capital District, Arson, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Capital District, Artists (1 of 2), 1923-1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Capital District, Artists (2 of 2), 1923-1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Capital District, Artists, 1937; 1955-1956; 1979; Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 12)
- Capital District, Arts, 1964-1965; 1978-1979; 1983; Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Capital District, Astronomy, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Capital District, Ballooning, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Capital District, Banking and Banks (1 of 2), 1943-1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Capital District, Banking and Banks (2 of 2), 1943-1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Capital District, Banking and Banks, 1950 (Oversized 1, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Bars and Taverns, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Capital District, Baseball, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Capital District, Beauty Operators, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Capital District, Beekeeping, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Capital District, Berkshire Women's News, 1986 (Oversized 1, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Billboards and Signs, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Capital District, Bioethics, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Capital District, Black People, 1940-1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Capital District, Blacksmiths, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Capital District, Blindness, 1955; 1960; 1965-1966; 1977-1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Capital District, Boating and Boats, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Capital District, Books, 1959-1979; Undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Capital District, Boycotts, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Capital District, Boys' Clubs, 1955-1956; 1966; 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Capital District, Boy Scouts of America, 1956-1979; Undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Capital District, Bridges and Dams (1 of 2), 1915-1980; Undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Capital District, Bridges and Dams (2 of 2), 1915-1980; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Capital District, Broadcasting, 1966; 1978; 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Capital District, Buildings, Historic (1 of 2), 1924-1983; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Capital District, Buildings, Historic (2 of 2), 1924-1983; Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Capital District, Buildings, Historic, 1955-1956; 1958; 1961 (Oversized 3, Folder 13)
- Capital District, Buildings, Historic, Preservation, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Capital District, Business and Industry (1 of 2), 1939-1981; Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Capital District, Business and Industry (2 of 2), 1939-1981; Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Capital District, Business and Industry, 1956; 1976 (Oversized 3, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Business Biography (1 of 2), 1971; 1975; 1977-1980 (Oversized 1, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Business Biography (2 of 2), 1971; 1975; 1977-1980 (Oversized 1, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Businesses, Minority-Owned, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Capital District, Camps, 1949; 1962; 1972-1973; 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Capital District, Cancer, 1973; 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Capital District, Canneries, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Capital District, Carnivals, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Capital District, Cars, Service Stations, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Capital District, Cartoonists, 1966; 1971; 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Catholicism (1 of 2), 1907-2002; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Catholicism (2 of 2), 1907-2002; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Caves, 1952-1980; Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Cemeteries, 1952; 1957; 1964-1965; 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Chambers of Commerce, 1967; 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Capital District, Charities and Community Services (1 of 2), 1937-1979; Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Capital District, Charities and Community Services (2 of 2), 1937-1979; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Capital District, Cheerleading, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Capital District, Chess, 1977 (Oversized 3, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Child Abuse, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Capital District, Christmas, ca. 1931 (Oversized 3, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Christmas, 1929-1984; Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Capital District, Churches, Baptist, 1936-1979; Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Capital District, Churches, Episcopal, 1922-1981; Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Capital District, Churches, Lutheran, 1959-1961; Undated; 1973; 1978 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Capital District, Churches, Methodist, 1936-1978; Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Capital District, Churches, Polish and Slovak, 1964-1966; 1970; 1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Capital District, Churches, Presbyterian, 1936-1979; Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Capital District, Churches, Reformed, 1936-1984; Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Capital District, Churches, Russian Orthodox, 1960-1961; 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Capital District, Circus, 1935; 1973; 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Capital District, Civil Defense, 1951-1980; Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Capital District, Civil War, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Capital District, Clubs and Professional Organizations, 1952-1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Capital District, Clubs, Rotary, 1955; 1966; 1969-1971; 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Capital District, Collecting, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Capital District, Colleges and Universities, 1968 (Oversized 3, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Colleges and Universities, 1975; 1977-1978; 1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Capital District, Comedians, 1978; Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Capital District, Commercial and Industrial Parks, 1962; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Capital District, Community Box Office, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Capital District, Community Development and Urban Renewal, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Capital District, Community Gardens, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Capital District, Conservation, Energy, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Capital District, Conservation, Consumer Cooperatives, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Capital District, Consumer Credit, 1961; 1965; 1969; 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Capital District, Cost of Living, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Capital District Council on Human Sexuality, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Capital District, Counterfeiting, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Capital District, Country Clubs, 1961-1964; 1966-1967; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Capital District, Courts, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Capital District, Courts, Family, 1972; 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Courts, Small Claims, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Crime, 1967-1968; 1971-1973; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Crime, Juvenile, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Crime Prevention, 1974; 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Criminal Justice, 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Capital District, Criminal Rehabilitation, 1974-1975; 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Capital District, Cults, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Capital District, Curling, 1956; 1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Capital District, Cycling, 1972-1973; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Capital District, Dance, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Capital District, Darts, 1978 (Oversized 1, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Deaf, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Capital District, Deaf Center, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Capital District, Dentists, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Capital District, Description, 1960-1980; Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Capital District, Dining, 1960-1981 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Capital District, Directories, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Capital District, Discotheques, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Capital District, Disease, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Capital District, Disorderly Conduct, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Capital District, Drug Abuse, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Capital District, Drugs and Youth, 1978-1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Capital District, Drugs, Enforcement, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Capital District, Drunk Driving, 1978-1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Capital District, Economy, 1961-1962; 1966; 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Capital District, Economy, 1979; 1981 (Oversized 3, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Education, Adult, 1965; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Capital District, Education, Computer-Assisted, 1977; 1979 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Capital District, Education, Reading, 1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Capital District Educational Opportunity Center, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Capital District, Elvis Impersonators, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Capital District, Emergency Services, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Capital District, Empire State Youth Orchestra, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Capital District, Employment and Unemployment, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Capital District, Energy Crisis, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Capital District, Environmental Conservation and Protection, 1960-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Capital District, Exhibitions, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Capital District, Fairs, 1957; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Capital District, Family Social Work, 1959; 1976-1977; 1979 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Capital District, Farms, 1965; 1974; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Capital District, Festivals, 1957; 1959; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Capital District, Films and Movie Theaters, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Capital District, Finances, Public, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Capital District, Fires and Fire Prevention, 1936-1981; Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Capital District, Fires and Fire Prevention, 1936-1937; 1959 (Oversized 3, Folder 19)
- Capital District, Fireworks, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Capital District, Fishing, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Capital District, Floods, 1936-1937; 1958; 1960; 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Capital District, Football, 1971; 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Capital District, Friends of Animals, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Capital District, Fundraising, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Capital District, Futurism, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Capital District, Gambling, 1971-1973; 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Capital District, Gardening, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Capital District, Gas and Gas Stations, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Capital District, Gay and Lesbian Rights, 1977-1981; Undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Capital District, Gender Bias, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Capital District, Girls' Centers and Clubs, 1960-1964; 1972; 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Capital District, Girl Scouts, 1957; 1966 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Capital District, Golf, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Capital District, Government and Politics, 1970; 1979 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Capital District, Gymnastics, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Capital District, Hang Gliding, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Capital District, Hauntings, 1968; 1970; 1978 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Capital District, High School Students, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Capital District, Highways, 1940; 1967 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Capital District, Hiking, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Capital District, Hispanics, 1975; 1978 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- Capital District, Historic Districts and Places, 1978-1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Capital District, History, C. Mooney's Column, 1958-1959; 1964; 1966-1969; 1971-1973; Undated (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Capital District, History, Religious Refugees, 1936 (Oversized 3, Folder 20)
- Capital District, History, Van Olindas' Column (1 of 2), 1940; 1953; 1955; 1957-1971; Undated (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Capital District, History, Van Olindas' Column (2 of 2), 1940; 1953; 1955; 1957-1971; Undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Capital District, Hocker, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Capital District, Home Care Service, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Capital District, Hospice Care, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Capital District, Hospitals, 1940-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Capital District, Hotels, 1936-1981; Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Capital District, Housing, 1973-1974; 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Capital District, Hunting, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Capital District, Ice and Snow, 1936-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Capital District, Ice and Snow, 1958 (Oversized 3, Folder 21)
- Capital District, Illiteracy, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Capital District, Indigenous Peoples, 1950; 1963-1964; 1968; Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Capital District, Industrial and Occupational Safety, 1962; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Capital District, Industrial and Scientific Research, 1956-1957; 1962; 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Capital District, Insurance, Fire, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Capital District, Insurance, Life, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Capital District, Iranians, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Capital District, Irish, 1978-1979; 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Capital District, Italians, 1978-1979; 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Jails, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Jews, 1957-1959; 1961; 1963; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Job Programs and Training, 1964-1966; 1977-1981; Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Judaism, 1954-1958; 1961; 1963-1966; 1968; Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Judges, 1972; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Capital District, Jurors, 1977; 1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Capital District, Lacrosse, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Capital District, Landlords and Tenants, 1973; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Capital District, Lawyers, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Capital District, Lead Contamination and Poisoning, 1972; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Capital District, Libraries, Public, 1936-1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Capital District, Liquor Laws, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Capital District, Litter, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, 1952-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, A, 1956-1985 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, B, 1955-1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, C, 1951-1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, D to F, 1956-1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, G, 1937-1986 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, H, 1917-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, I to K, 1956-1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, L to M, 1956-1986; Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, N to R, 1929-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, S, 1938-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, T, 1957-1961; 1963; 1966 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, U to V, 1949; 1952; 1958-1967; 1971; Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, W, 1958-1961; 1963-1964; 1967; 1977; Undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Capital District, Local Luminaries, X to Z, 1956; 1962; 1977 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Capital District, Maternity Care, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Capital District, Medical Care, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Capital District, Memorial Day, 1963; 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Capital District, Mental Health, 1969; 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Capital District, Meteorology, 1959; 1961; 1970-1971; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Capital District, Middle Class, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Capital District, Minorities, Employment, 1970; 1972; 1981 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Capital District, Monuments and Statues, 1917-1978; Undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Capital District, Music, 1961-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Capital District, National Society for Autistic Children, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Capital District, Newspapers, 1953-1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Capital District, Nursing, 1960; 1975; 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Capital District, Older People, 1952-1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Capital District, Opera, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Capital District, Organized Labor, 1962; 1974-1975; 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Capital District, Parenting, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Capital District, Parking, 1937-1961; Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Capital District, Parks and Recreation, 1900-1980; Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Capital District, Persons with Disabilities, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Capital District, Pharmacists, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Capital District, Photographers, 1951; 1967; 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Capital District, Physicians, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Capital District, Playgrounds, 1950; 1965-1967; 1975; 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Capital District, Police, 1964; 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Capital District, Polish, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Capital District, Political Posters, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Capital District, Pollution, Air, 1973; 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Capital District, Pollution, Water, 1971-1972; 1978-1979; 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Pornography, 1979; 1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Postal Service, 1971; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Potholes, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Poverty, 1973; 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Poverty, Rural, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Capital District, Prices, 1979; Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Capital District, Psychotherapy, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Capital District, Public Health and Safety, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Capital District, Puppeteers, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Capital District, Racquetball, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Capital District, Radio, 1960; 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Capital District, Radioactivity, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Capital District, Railroads, 1936-1979; Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Capital District, Rape, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Capital District, Rats, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Capital District, Recreational Activities, 1957; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Capital District, Recreational Activities, 1977-1979 (Oversized 3, Folder 22)
- Capital District, Recycling and Waste Disposal, 1972-1974; 1977-1981; Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Capital District Regional Planning Commission, 1970; 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Capital District, Religion, 1959-1980; Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Capital District, Religious Orders, 1959-1960; 1963; 1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Capital District, Republican Party, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Capital District, Revenue Sharing, 1971; 1980 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Capital District, Road Races, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Capital District, Rugby, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Capital District, Salvation Army, 1961-1978; Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Capital District, Saving and Investment, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Capital District, Schools, Independent, 1936-1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Capital District, Schools, Public (1 of 2), 1957-1980; Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Capital District, Schools, Public (2 of 2), 1957-1980; Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Capital District, Schools, Religious, 1939-1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Capital District, Scottish, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Capital District, Sewage and Sewers, 1947; 1972; 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Capital District, Sex Education, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Capital District, Sex Work, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Capital District, Shakers, 1936-1985; Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Capital District, Sheriffs, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Capital District, Shoplifting, 1978; 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Capital District, Shopping Centers and Stores, 1956-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Capital District, Shriners, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Capital District, Skateboarding, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Capital District, Ski Areas, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Capital District, Softball, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Capital District, Solar Energy, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Capital District, Sports, 1979; 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Capital District, Sports, College, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Capital District, Sports, High School, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Capital District, Sports, Professional, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Capital District, Spousal Abuse, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Capital District, Substance Abuse, Prevention and Treatment, 1970; 1975; 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Capital District, Swimming, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Capital District, Tax Foreclosures and Sales, 1974; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Capital District, Teen Drinking, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Capital District, Teen Pregnancy, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Capital District, Television (1 of 2), 1972-1974; 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Capital District, Television (2 of 2), 1972-1974; 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Capital District, Tennis, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Capital District, Theater and Theaters, 1963; 1977-1979; 1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Capital District, Tourism, 1957-2000; Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Capital District, Track and Field, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Capital District, Traffic Flow, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Capital District, Traffic Safety, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Capital District, Transportation, 1959; 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Capital District, Transportation Authority, 1971; 1973-1975; 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Capital District, Transportation Committee, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Capital District, Travelers Aid Society, 1958; 1962-1963; 1978 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Capital District, Ugandans, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Capital District, Ukrainians, 1969; 1979 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Capital District, Undocumented Noncitizens, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Capital District, Unwed Fathers, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Capital District, Vandalism, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Capital District, Veterans, 1962; 1973; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Capital District, Veterinarians, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Capital District, Vietnam War, 1965-1972 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Capital District, Vietnamese, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Capital District, Views, 1958-1978; Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Capital District, Vocational Guidance, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Capital District, Volunteering, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Capital District, War Memorials, 1954-1987 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Capital District, Washington, George, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Capital District, Water Supply, 1934-1981 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Capital District, Water Supply, 1938; 1953; 1964-1965 (Oversized 3, Folder 23)
- Capital District, Weightlifting, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Capital District, Welfare, 1973; 1975; 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Capital District, Widowed Persons Service, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Capital District, Women in Politics, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Capital District, YMCA, 1961-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Capital District, Youth, At-risk, Assistance, 1960; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Capital District, Youth, At-risk, Facilities, 1957-1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Capital District, Youth Centers and Programs, 1973; 1977; 1979 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Capital District, Youth Employment, 1964-1965; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Capital District, Youth with Disabilities, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Capital District, YWCA, 1959-1961; 1966; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Capital District, Zoning (1 of 2), 1967; 1972-1974; 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Capital District, Zoning (2 of 2), 1967; 1972-1974; 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Chautauqua, 1909; 1919; 1923; 1927; Undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Clarksville, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Claverack, 1956; 1974 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Clifton Park, 1974-1975; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)